travelyosemite.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Yosemite National Park, CA

Effective August 1, 2015

Aramark is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Web site.

  * Information Collected:
  * Use of Collected Information
  * Links to Other Sites
  * Security of Collected Information
  * Access to Collected Information
  * Contacting Us
  * Changes to this Policy
  * Candidate Data Privacy Protection

**Information Collected**

In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a 'cookie' (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site, and to Aramark services on other sites. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation and to measure the effectiveness of our promotional placements, and is not shared with anyone other than Aramark affiliates and contractors who assist Aramark in these efforts and are bound to confidentiality. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.

In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address. For our supplier diversity area, we necessarily collect information about gender and ethnicity, such as whether your business is female-owned.

Information obtained from our Careers Section will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating your submission for possible employment and the related purposes described on our jobs site. In the event you provide us with any information requested in the Careers section of this Web Site, your submission will be governed by our Candidate Data Protection Standard, a copy of which is displayed below.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

This website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.

**Use of Collected Information**

Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.

When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information, such as the Careers section of our Web Site. Usually, we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive electronic annual reports, to be added to our supplier diversity database or to process your request for employment). This information may be shared with other Aramark businesses, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes.

We may share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies - our vendors - are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances.

If you register with one of Aramark's business units online, they may use this information to provide you with custom information about Aramark offerings in support of your business needs. They may also seek to place a 'cookie' (small data file) as discussed above in order to provide you with tailored information. You should review the privacy policy associated with that Aramark business' Web site for further information on privacy practices.

If you stay in lodging operated by Aramark in a national park, we may share information about you, such as a mailing address, with a non-profit organization or organizations supporting the park.  We do not otherwise share, sell, or lease personal information about you to third parties for their direct marketing use.

How can you stop receiving email from us?

\- Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from Aramark Leisure. If you wish to do so, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

\- You can also unsubscribe by postal mail. Write to us and let us know you wish to opt-out of email marketing communications. Send your letter to:

Aramark Leisure  
Attn: Marketing Department  
2850 E. Camelback Road  
Suite 240  
Phoenix, AZ 85016

**Links to Other Sites**

Aramark's Web site may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.

**Security of Collected Information**

We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those Aramark workers who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.

**Access to Collected Information**

You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this Web site by contacting us as described below.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Web site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.

**Candidate Data Privacy Protection**

I. OBJECTIVE

The objective of these Candidate Data Protection Standards (“Standards”) is to provide adequate and consistent safeguards for the handling of candidate data by Aramark entities. These Standards are designed with the intention of defining Aramark’s protection of Candidate Data. Aramark is committed to fair information practices that are compliance with applicable, local law. The identifiable information about yourself that you or someone else provides (on your or Aramark’s behalf) to an Aramark entity in the context of applying for a position with an Aramark entity (the “Candidate Data” or “Data”) will be used for recruitment purposes and the Candidate Data will be protected in accordance with Aramark’s Standards outlined below and applicable law.

The identifiable information about yourself that you or someone else provides (on your or Aramark’s behalf) to an Aramark entity will be used for recruitment purposes and the Candidate Data will be protected in accordance with Aramark’s Standards outlined below and applicable law.

By submitting your Candidate Data, you confirm and agree that:

You have reviewed Aramark’s Standards and Privacy Policy;

Aramark and/or its third party service providers may process the Candidate Data according to the recruitment purposes set out in the Standards; The Candidate Data may be transferred to other Aramark entities consistent with Aramark’s Standards; and your consent is required in order to complete the submittal process. If you do not agree to abide by these terms and conditions do not use the site. Aramark may periodically collect further information with your consent or in accordance with applicable laws. For example, Aramark may require additional information to perform background checks or obtain approvals, which may be a condition to employment. In addition, Aramark may collect your feedback and opinions (e.g., surveys) for business purposes, such as improving processes.

II. PURPOSES AND ACCESS FOR CANDIDATE DATA PROCESSING

Aramark and Aramark entities process Candidate Data for legitimate human resources purposes. Such processing will be conducted within such purpose limitations and in accordance with applicable law.

III. SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY

Aramark entities are committed to taking appropriate technical, physical, and organizational measures to protect Candidate Data against unauthorized access, unlawful processing, accidental loss or damage, and unauthorized destruction.

Equipment and Information Security

To safeguard against unauthorized access to Candidate Data by third parties outside Aramark, all electronic Candidate Data held by Aramark entities are maintained on systems that are protected by secure network architectures that contain firewalls and intrusion detection devices. The servers are stored in facilities with comprehensive security and fire detection and response systems.

Access Security

Aramark entities limit access to internal systems that hold Candidate Data to a select group of authorized users who are given access to such systems through the use of a unique identifier and password. Access to Candidate Data is limited to and provided to individuals for the purpose of performing their job duties (e.g., a human resources manager may need access to a Candidate’s contact information for the purposes of setting up an interview).

IV. DIRECT MARKETING

Aramark entities will not disclose Candidate Data outside Aramark to offer any products or services to a Candidate for personal or familial consumption (“direct marketing”) without his or her prior consent. The restrictions in this section apply only to contact data obtained in the context of applying for a position with Aramark and not, for example, to data obtained in the context of a customer relationship.
